evergent.com 2019-06-15

# Privacy Policy - Evergent

Last modified: [09/05/2017]

## Introduction

Evergent Technologies, Inc. (“ **Evergent** ” or **** “ **We** ”) respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the Evergent web site (the “ **Website** ”) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On the Website.
  * In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and the Website.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Evergent or any third party; or
  * any third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from the Website.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to Our Privacy Policy). Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

## Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It

We may collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

  * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number (“ **personal information** ”);
  * that is about you but individually does not identify you; and/or
  * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details.

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies.

**Information You Provide to Us**.  
The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This may include information provided at the time of registering to use our Website or information we request from you from time to time.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, “ **posted** ”) on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, “ **User Contributions** ”). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. We cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

**Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies**.  
As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and does not include personal. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better service.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.

## How We Use Your Information

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

## Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose aggregated information about our users and information that does not identify any individual without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply the terms and conditions of use of the Website.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Evergent, its customers, or others.

## Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information

You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page with a notice that the privacy policy has been updated on the Website home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

## Contact Information

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:

Evergent Technologies, Inc.  
1250 Borregas Avenue  
Sunnyvale, CA 94089
